[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The endangered Komodo dragon is the largest living lizard in the world, growing to an average length of 2-3 meters (10 feet).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The lizards which do not have legs are commonly known by what name?", "correct_answer": "Glass lizards", "incorrect_answers": ["Monitor lizards", "Skinks", "Iguanas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest known impact crater on Mercury is named what?", "correct_answer": "Caloris Basin", "incorrect_answers": ["Olymus Mons", "Tyco Crater", "Skinakas Basin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city, located in Colorado, is the highest city in the United States.", "correct_answer": "Leadville", "incorrect_answers": ["Vail", "Colorado Springs", "Denver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "British aircraft manufacturer, Saunders Roe, developed the first practical man-carrying hovercraft, the SR-N1. Its first public demonstration, including a cross-channel run, was made in what year?", "correct_answer": "1959", "incorrect_answers": ["1716", "1934", "1978"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why are portholes typically round?", "correct_answer": "To spread out pressure on the the ships covering", "incorrect_answers": ["Because a circle gives you the most area for the least perimeter.", "For easier and smoother entering from the outside", "They are circular by ancient tradition."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the last name of the man credited with inventing the modern bicycle?", "correct_answer": "Michaux", "incorrect_answers": ["Bremen", "Wright", "Turnbull"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only original movie, included in the AFI Top 100 list, together with its sequel?", "correct_answer": "Godfather and Godfather  II", "incorrect_answers": ["Stars Wars (Episode 4)  and 5", "Indiana Jones 1 and 2", "Star Wars 1 and 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the American version of Monopoly, which are the two most expensive properties?", "correct_answer": "Boardwalk and Park Place", "incorrect_answers": ["Boardwalk and Fifth Avenue", "Broadway and North Carolina Avenue.", "Boardwalk and  Ventnor Avenue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chocolate cannot kill a dog.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1931 movie that contains the quote,  Listen to them, the children of the night. What music they make.", "correct_answer": "Dracula", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wolfman", "The Devils Castle", "Curse of the Demon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "B1, a vitamin participating in many important cellular processes, is synthesized by animals, plants and some bacteria.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]